Pallavi Daswani

Student

High school graduate with 1 year experience of being a part of the organising team in our School for multiple events such as sports, food and cultural tests.

College student with a record of academic and extracurricular success.

Adept at working across departments, with faculty, administrators, and students.

Current studying BBA at Symbiosis College, Viman Nagar, Pune.

Personal Info

Address

Flat no.205, Nina Apartments Synagogue Street, Camp Pune, Maharashtra.

Phone

9579226636

E-mail

pallavidaswani99@gmail.com

Place of birth

Tenerife, Spain

Date of birth

1999-12-03

Skills

Basic knowledge of MS Excel (macros, pivot tables, data visualization)Proficient in MS Access (creating and modifying databases, tables, queries and forms; reports) moderate.

project Management time management.

Languages

SPANISH FRENCH

Experience

2019-01

VICE PRESIDENT AT SYMBIOSIS INTERNATIONAL STUDENT COUNCIL 2019-20.

Organising international events for international students all over Pune. Events which include Dance, sports, convocation ceremony, flag presentation etc.

This help us in growing a person and managing every kind of event that would teach us something new.

CORE committee at Sympulse Fest held at SCMS Campus, Pune.

SIMUNC(SYMBIOSIS INTERNATIONAL MODEL UNITED NATION CONFERENCE)

Organising SIMUNC department for 3 days with our other core members and creating a whole different experience for the people participating in our event.

Learnt how to coordinate with people and have a friendly relations with the other teams.

Making new friends from different parts of India. overall great experience.

2017-05

HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT INTERNSHIP

ME CURE INDUSTRIES LTD.

Amazing experience working and learning from the employees in this industry.

One week internship created a whole different aspect in my life by how things work in a company compare to what we are taught in school.

Got a wide experience on how Accounting and Human Resource management works on daily basis.

FIRST YEAR COLLEGE INTERNSHIP

PLASKA INDUSTRIES LTD. (NIGERIA)

Had an amazing experience working and learning from the employees in this industry.

One month internship created a whole different aspect in my life by how things work in a company.

Got a wide experience on how Accounting (TALLY) and Human Resource management works on daily basis.

Education

2003

2009

LOS CHRISTIANOS SCHOOL, TENERIFE, SPAIN.

Born in Spain and studied there till GRADE 4.

Learnt their basic Spanish language and participated and small kids competitions.

Participated at ICC(INDIAN CULTURE ASSOCIATION if Spain) for dance competitions every year.

2009

2018

INDIAN LANGUAGE SCHOOL, LAGOS, NIGERIA, HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATE.

Studied from grade 4 to grade 12 i.e.9 years of my life in NIGERIA. Inculcated their values and understandings on their local culture. participated in various competitions especially sports and dance. actively studies and performed various online courses.

2018

2021

CURRENTLY PURSUING BBA at SYMBIOSIS COLLEGE, VIMAN NAGAR, PUNE.

Specialising in Human Resource and International Business.

Certificates

2017

PARTICIPATION IN ECOVISIONNARIE, INDIA.

2017-10

FIRST PRIZE IN TABLE TENNIS GIRLS DOUBLES.

2016

FIRST PRIZE IN MAGAZINE COVER COMPETITON.

2017

THIRD PRIZE IN BADMINTON GIRLS.

2018-07

CERTIFICATE FOR COMPLETION AND PARTICIPATION FOR MICROECONOMICS ONLINE COURSE.

2018

ONLINE COURSE FOR MS EXCEL 2010- REVISED 2017

ONINE COURSE FOR FUNDAMENTALS OF FINANCIAL ACCOUNTING- REVISED 2017

2019

CERTIFICATE FOR PARTICIPATION OF ONLINE SWAYAM COURSE ON OPERATIONAL RESEARCH AND MICROECONOMICS.

COMPLETION OF ONLINE COURSE ON MANAGEMENT ACCOUNTING.

AWARD RECEIVED FOR ORGANISING THE CONVOCATION CEREMONY OF INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS.

FIRST PRIZE IN BADMINTON DOUBLES- INTERNATIONAL SPORTS.

CERTIFICATE FOR BEING PART OF THE CORE COMMITTEE IN SYIMBIOSIS MUN.

CERTIFICATE FOR BEING PART OF STEP UP CLUB CREW FOR A YEAR.

Interests

SPORTS- BADMINTON AND TABLE TENNIS.

MAKING NEW FRIENDS FROM ANY PART OF THE WORLD AND MANAGING EVENTS FOR STUDENTS.

EXPLORING DAILY LIFE FACTS.

ACTIVE ON SOCIAL MEDIA AND CREATING SHORT ACTING VIDEOS AS A PART OF MY HOBBY.